One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
Heaven and Earth
How dare that punk do that?!
Before Lucy comes to,
this country will be shred to pieces!
We gotta do something about it ourselves!
Take down Doflamingo, and the bird cage goes away!
You really are dense.
My message to you should be clear:
"Give me Straw Hat."
Gatz-san, Lucy still needs more time to recover!
But I believe many people will die before that happens!
I know! But I can't send
an incapacitated fighter into the ring!
Whatever happens,
I won't give him up before he's recovered!
Who's there?
T... T-T-Trafalgar Law!
The W-W-Warlo...
You guys... don't you think you're running too much?
Oh, that's because... Um...
Will he regain his Haki?
O-Oh, the thing is...
He told me that he needed ten minutes,
and now we've got three minutes and twenty seconds to go!
No time to lose, then.
I'll take care of him from here.
Okay!
Less than three minutes remain
until the bird cage closes completely.
Sevio
Barrier!
Now, let's do this, guys!
My barrier will never break!
Push!
Follow Zoro-senpai!
King!
All together now, and push!
How strange.
How can they exert that much power
with those injured bodies?
Just a few minutes ago, they were burned out
and couldn't even stand up.
What was all that fluff?
They were Dandehealions.
"Dandehealions"?
That's right!
They're dandelions made from Princess Mansherry's tears.
Wait for me, wait for me!
Hurry up, or you'll get torn to shreds!
Run faster!
I can't, dammit!
I can't believe I twisted my ankle at a time like this!
Hang in there!
Huh?! I can run!
He's way too fast! What's going on?!
Dandehealion petals can miraculously heal people over a wide area.
Princess Mansherry is worried about
what's happening to Dressrosa,
and so she's shedding tears.
I truly believe it will save many lives!
So that's why those previously immobile fighters are...
However, the drawback of this ability is...
that it's only a temporary recovery, lasting for just a few minutes!
It's unfortunate, but they'll revert to their
former state when time's up!
So this is a last-ditch life support measure for our survival!
The pain just suddenly left!
I can run! I can escape!
It's a miracle, doctor!
The gods themselves must have descended to save our country!
Kabu-san...
Yes, Princess Mansherry?
This is how I fight!
I don't know how to use weapons,
and I can't bring down bad people, but...
the tears won't stop!
Yes, it's very you!
An honorable way to fight!
How in the...
The injured are recovering, one after another!
Let's just get outta here!
Hey, wait a minute!
Heed my voice!
What is it, Hundredth-Degree Hack?!
No, the guy behind him!
It's the five-star, God Usopp!
Just what kind of crime did he commit?!
Alright, listen up, men!
The strong among you need to go to the east and west sides of town!
My friends are pushing back the bird cage in those places!
Give 'em a hand!
Help them push back the bird cage?
I don't think there's even a way to stop that thing!
Yeah, there's no way!
Quit making excuses! Believe in my friends!
It's the wrath of God!
We're on it!
Run!
Hurry up!
Everybody, don't abandon hope!
There are people who haven't yet given up!
Come on, hurry up!
Thank you, Rebecca!
They're all trying so hard to stop the bird cage...
But if this bird cage really is unstoppable,
all of their efforts will be wasted!
I know I'm no match for him, but...
But everybody's fighting at their hardest!
I've got to do something, too!
Father... If push comes to shove, I'll...
kill Doflamingo!
Viola-san!
Rebecca! Why are you here?!
Viola-san, I...
Don't do anything foolish!
If I allow you to die, I won't be able to face Kyros, nor my late sister!
So, what did you come to see me for, Viola?
The Donquixote Family is about to be obliterated.
If I do nothing to take responsibility as a
former commander, it would be too selfish of me.
You can't!
Either I die, or you die!
Doffy!
You're ever the passionate one, Violet.
Town Center
Hey, we've come all this way! Just let us through!
The bird cage is right there!
They say there's danger ahead,
and we can barely advance here as well!
People all over the country arrived here
at the same time, so we can't even move!
Smile Factory
You gotta push more! Push harder!
The bird cage will definitely stop! Just keep pushing!
We got it!
Vicinity of the Smile Factory
At the Bird Cage
How are we faring?
It's slowing down... I think!
Now that you mention it,
it does appear to be slowing down!
Why are you here?!
Oh my... I can't tell who's there, as I'm blind.
Crap!
It's hard to leave behind such a band of fools, is it not?
Please allow me to assist in even the slightest capacity, despite my limited ability!
Company, halt!
Support those "unknown" people pushing the cage!
Aye aye, sir!
The Navy?!
Oh, quite the aid!
This is encouraging!
Those of you unable to use Haki, head for the factory!
Aye aye, sir!
The Navy?!
Push the bird cage back!
R-Run for it!
Hey, what're you doing?!
Nothing'll change if we just keep running!
I'm gonna push, too!
H-Hey!
Push!
Oh, dammit, I'll push, too!
I'm no weakling!
Yeah, that's the spirit!
Me neither!
We're gonna push, too!
We wanna defend our own country!
Push it, all together now!
Alright, you guys!
Give it everything you've got!
Yeah!
Sevio
There they are!
Warriors, let us push too!
Get pushing already!
Yeah!
Us, too!
We can't just let it cut us without doing anything!
Thank you all! I'm counting on you!
Yeah, let's work together!
Here we go, guys!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Push!
It's moving again!
But it did stop for a moment.
So it's stoppable!
Zoro-senpai is as awesome as ever!
Keep pushing! Let's stall the shutting of the bird cage!
Stay focused!
Hold on! Put more into it!
What... Your Majesty? Army Commander Tank?
Well done!
If it weren't for you all,
we would've lost thousands already!
Screw this bird cage!
People are meant to be free! Keep pushing!
Yes, sir!
More!
Push the bird cage back!
That's enough, Viola-san!
Viola-san!
A decade...
Did you really think I would hesitate just because
we spent all that time together as a Family, Violet?
That I would hesitate to kill you?
I don't criticize my associates
for their mistakes.
However, I don't condone betrayal.
And now, next up is...
Look at her, Violet!
Rebecca!
Viola-san... I can't control my body...
Poor girl. She's so scared.
You can't!
Now, right this way!
Stop it! Don't involve Rebecca!
What am I... doing?!
Viola-san!
Rebecca!
No! I don't wanna do this!
Now, kill her.
Viola-san!
Why am I doing this?!
Rebecca!
I don't wanna do this!
Viola-san!
It's starting to slice up the old Royal Grounds!
Damn! It stopped once!
If it keeps closing in,
people will start dying one after another!
Don't give up! Keep pushing!
Stall it even for a second!
How long till Lucy's back up?
Uh, let me see...
Time until the slowed bird cage closes completely:
sixty seconds.
Time remaining until Lucy's comeback:
It stopped once!
We can keep on holding it back!
Stop the cage!
Stand strong and hang in there!
Shut up! You're distracting us!
Let's make this the greatest thing we've ever done!
Please... Please be safe...
As many lives as possible...
Alright, everyone!
It won't be much longer!
Wh-Who's talking?
Who is that? Now isn't the time!
Where is he shouting from?
Our star shall return!
Oh, hey!
There he is!
You're the announcer from the Colosseum, Gatz!
When did you get up there?
And what are you up to?
Everyone, have you forgotten?
Now isn't the time to fool around!
Our country is on the verge of destruction!
You aren't the king!
No, of course you haven't forgotten!
That funny, bold star who burst onto the scene...
in the tournament at the Corrida Colosseum today!
Star?!
Don't tell me he's talking about...
...me!
Well, I told you I'd stay here with you, but would you mind if I departed?
Trafal...
Gah! Law! He's gone!
What... where did he go?!
I have not forgotten.
He tamed the killer bull feared by all,
and toppled the towering Giant!
He even knocked out the living legend, Don Chinjao!
The little gladiator who made the Colosseum...
nay, the whole of Dressrosa burst with excitement!
Never before have I seen anyone fight so freely,
and make a competition as thrilling as he did!
I was there watching it!
He's talking about that guy, isn't he?
I saw him at the Colosseum!
I watched it on a screen in town!
And his name is...
Lucy!
So what? He's just some gladiator!
Lucy...
Help me, Lucy...
That's right! It's Lucy!
But that was just an alias!
His real name is...
The pirate, Straw Hat...
Luffy!
Wha... that's who Lucy was under his mask?
Since we've been fooled by
and been under the control of a pirate,
it's probably difficult for us to trust another pirate!
However...
He's different from the Donquixote Family, who appeared disguised as heroes,
on that night a decade ago!
Straw Hat Luffy is the man that our true king,
King Riku, called our "hope"!
Right now, he's knocked out after being wounded in battle, but...
It's not over yet!
Tremble with joy, Dressrosa!
Lucy...
swore this to me!
Doflamingo will...
...be KOed in a single blow!
He's got a hell of a big mouth!
You've gotta do it...
We can't hold out much longer, Luffy!
Amazing!
Lucy!
Are you listening,
Doflamingo?!
You...
used our king as a puppet, deceived the world,
and lived here in Dressrosa as a false king!
This will be your...
execution stand!
Gatz...
I see everything you're up to, Doflamingo!
If you want me, come and get me!
Stay away from Viola-sama and Rebecca-sama!
It won't be long before the star forged in the Colosseum,
Lucy, comes back!
Until that moment comes, hang in there!
Luffy-senpai! Here we go!
Hajrudin!
What the...
The injured who recovered earlier are collapsing again!
Time's up.
The effects of the Dandehealions on the initial recipients are wearing off.
And it won't work twice in a row!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
All because I don't have the strength...
I lifted them up for a moment,
only to drop them right back down! I'm awful!
No, Princess Mansherry.
If it weren't for the Dandehealions, who knows how many people would have died from the bird cage!
But...
Look!
You've created a miracle!
Oh, please! What weaklings!
People in the back take the places of the fallen! And bring more people!
Yeah!
We'll hold out no matter what,
until Lucy frees us from the bird cage!
Yeah!
They've held out long enough.
Luffyland will take over from there and rid us of the bird cage!
And now the moment you've been waiting for...
Lucy will come back in ten seconds!
He should be somewhere, listening! Call out our star's name!
Lucy! Lucy!
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!
Three seconds to go!
Two!
Gatz-san!
Lucy! Lucy!
One!
Ludicrous.
Go to hell, Doflamingo!
Our star Lucy's gonna...
drop you with a single blow!
Zero!
Viola, it's your turn to be silenced.
Forever.
No!
Viola-san!
Close your eyes, Rebecca!
You don't have to see a thing!
This is just a bad dream!
No matter what happens, forget everything!
I won't hold a grudge against you so...
just forget about it, okay?
No!
It's not your fault at all!
I'm so sorry, Rebecca!
This will leave a deep scar in your heart!
No!
Go!
He has come!
Lucy!
Lucy! Lucy!
Straw Hat...
A flashy comeback, I suppose.
But you've barely managed to regain your Haki.
You must barely be able to stand, no?
That...
goes for you too, right?!
Lucy!
Chambres!
Rebecca!
There you are.
Well, watch closely, then...
as your hope is crushed.
Everwhite!
Th-The entire town's turned to strings!
Lucy!
Why, you...
Futile.
Thousand Arrows!
Flapping...
Thread!
Armament!
What's the matter?
I thought you were back at full strength?
Have you really regained your Haki, Lucy?
I-Is he gonna be okay?
Lucy!
That was pretty loud!
It's too dusty to see clearly.
Did Lucy win?
The bird cage is still here!
Hurry up, Lucy!
Wh-What the...
My body's moving on its own...
I can't believe you're still alive!
Shall I impale you?
Is that why you came running back?
You made it out alive again, Luffy.
Hmph! Next time I'll win!
What happened to that Kong Gun you're so proud of?
Well, it's like this, Rayleigh!
This guy was way, way bigger than the other one...
So it didn't work!
That's quite the problem.
But if the Kong Gun isn't working,
you have to come up with something else.
Something else?
Amusing, isn't it?
Every single one of you...
would have been better off staying in my cage and submitting to my manipulation.
Cage?
Manipulation?
Humans are mere scum.
Enough, already!
The Royal Plateau is getting cut!
Hurry up, Luffy!
Gonna do it again?
If you turn into that Bound-Man of yours, I won't just have you kill your friends...
but everyone in the country!
Gear Fourth!
The strings-!
You've barely got any stamina left. How many seconds can you stay in that form?
Lucy!
He chose to fight me midair?
He's got guts!
Will I get to see how you're gonna "one-hit KO" me?!
It's annoying to have you stand over me!
You're always trying to chain down anything and everything...
...and controlling and manipulating everybody!
I feel like I'm suffocating!
Blame your own birthright!
All of you were born trash, fit only for manipulation!
You humans are different from me!
Shut up!
I'm gonna kick your ass and get outta here!
Do your worst, brat!
Spiderweb!
But if the Kong Gun isn't working,
you have to come up with something else.
Rubber...
Something else?
That's right.
Gear Fourth taxes your body far too much.
You've got to think of something else.
How about this, then?
What?
That'll just make the problem even worse!
King Kong...
If you won't obey, I'll just kill you!
Sixteen Holy Bullets!
God Thread!
...Gun!
And in a certain land, there are people who call the Family of "D"...
"the sworn enemy of the gods"!